Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Subject Files
  - Lyotard, Jean-François, 1980-2000 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Mabou Mines, c. 1980 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Mabou Mines, Undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Mailer, Norman - dossier, Undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Mailer, Norman, Undated (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Malka, Gabriella, Undated (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Manon Lescout, Undated (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Media, Undated (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Meinhof, Undated (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Miller, David (artist), 1990's (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Mielions, Undated (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - "The Miracle of Lascaux" clippings, receipts, etc..., c. 1989 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Modernism / Holocaust, Undated (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Muller, Heiner, Undated (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Murray, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Negri, Toni, Undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Negri, Toni: Italian Book, Undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Negri, Toni / Virno and Empire, Undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Nepal, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - No Sex, Undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Nouveau Roman, Undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Oldenburg, Claes, Undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Olivenstein, Claude, c. 1997 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Oppenheim, Dennis / Contemporary Art, Undated (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Ottinger, Ulrike, Undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Pacific Rim, New Zealand, Undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Painting, 1982-1989 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Palestine, Charlemagne, Undated (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Pane, Gina, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - PAT dept., 2006 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Peguy and the affair, Undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Plagiarism, Undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Pleynet, Genette, Undated (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Plouha, Undated (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Porto Rico, 1980's (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Postmodernism (1 of 2), Undated (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Postmodernism (2 of 2), Undated (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Prevues and evidences, Undated (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Proust / Deleuze, Undated (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Psychology, Undated (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Rabi, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Rainer, Yvonne, Undated (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Rammell Zee, Undated (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Reich, Steve, Undated (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Représentatión and inteurité, 1970's (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Ricardon, c. 1975 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Ritual Murder, Undated (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Rock, c. 1977 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    Full newspapers removed to oversize.
  - Rolnik, Suely, 1990's (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Romans, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Roman du Moyen âge, Undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Roman (17e), 1963-1970 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Roman (19e), Undated (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Rupp, Christy, Undated (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Ryan, Paul / Willoughby Sharp interview, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Sacher-Masoch, undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - "Sade 1980" (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - "Sade 1980" (2 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - S&M, undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - S&M texts, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Saussure - "Anagrammes", circa 1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Saussure (1 of 2), circa 1974 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Saussure (2 of 2), circa 1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Scalzone - printed texts, interviews (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Scemama - photos, contact sheets, undated (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Schoener, Allen, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Scientology, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Segalen, Victor, circa 1989 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Semantique, undated (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Semiotique, undated (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Semiotique des intensités (1 of 2), undated (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Semiotique des intensités (2 of 2), Undated (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Serra, Richard, Undated (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Serrano, Andres, Undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Sex Dossier, 1980's (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Sexual Deviations, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Sexuality and Literature, Undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D., Undated (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D.: Adler, Undated (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D.: Adler, Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D.: Adler, Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Shands, Harley C., M.D.: Adler; including interview transcript, Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Shelton, Ann, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Sherman, Stuart, 1980's (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Situationism, Undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Jack, 1980's - 1990's (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Kiki, Undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Smith, Robertson - including William Burroughs interview, 1990's (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Spaid, Sue, Undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Spero, Nancy, undated (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Spero, Nancy, 1990s (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Sprinkle, Annie, undated (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Steir, Pat (included Ricard Foreman layouts), undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Stylistique/Structuralisme, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Surveillance Films, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Symbole/Signe, undated (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Teaching Humanities, undated (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Thevenin, Paul on Artaud paintings, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - "Things Happen", undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Tillman, Lynne, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Tillman, Lynne - Bio and clipping packet, undated (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Tillman, Lynne - Texts, undated (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Trieste, undated (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Trockel, Rosemarie, undated (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Ultimatum, undated (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Ungar, Steven, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Virilio, Paul (1 of 2), circa 2000 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Virilio, Paul (2 of 2), circa 2000 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Virilio (includes manuscripts), undated (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Virilio, undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Virilio dissertation, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Von Praunheim, Rosa - Films 1976-1886, undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - War, circa 1984 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Weil, Simone, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Weil, Simone - Attente de Dieu, undated (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Weil, Simone - Factory Journals, undated (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Weil, Simone - Textes, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Whitney, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Wilson, Bob, 1970s/1980s (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Bob, undated (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - "Yurik", 1984 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Series V: Sylvère Lotringer Projects
  This series assembles the body of Sylvère Lotringer's work that is not directly related to the Semiotext(e) group. It contains subseries for his writing (including his book on sex offenders, Overexposed); his film projects, often in collaboration with his then-wife Chris Kraus; conferences, events and tours that he organized or participated in as an individual; academic papers, personal papers, and a subseries of notes and fragments. User discretion is advised for materials related to Overexposed, which may contain descriptions of sexual violence.
  - Subseries A: Writing
    Contains drafts, proofs and notes pertaining to writing projects that Sylvere Lotringer worked on which do not appear under the Semiotext(e) name. Materials are arranged alphabetically by project title, where alternate titles are known they are indicated in parentheses. Within a project, materials are arranged alphabetically.
    - "A Pavilion in Time" (alternate title "Ghosts"), undated (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - "A Pavilion in Time" (alt title "Ghosts"), undated (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - "About Face", undated (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - "Agent de l'etranger" (Lotringer interviewed by Ganahl), 1997 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - "The Algebra of News", circa 1983 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - "The Anthropology of Unhappiness", Undated (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - "The Anthropology of Unhappiness", undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - "The Anthropology of Unhappiness" (Duras, Antelme - unpublished), undated (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - "Artaud Juif" (includes published clippings), undated (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - "Artaud le Moma" early draft for "Artaud on Paper" at MOMA (includes correspondence), circa 1997 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - "Argo-Notes", circa 1970 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - "Artaud le MOMA" (edited version - incomplete), circa 1997 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - "Artaud le MOMA", circa 1997 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - "Artaud le MOMA" (includes copies of published texts), circa 1997 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - "Artaud's doubles" includes "Artaud and Theatre" book proposal, undated (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - "L'Astree", undated (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - "Ball of Fat", circa 1992 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - "Ball of Fat" with Maupassant source text, circa 1992 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - "Ball of Fat" with slides, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - "Baudrillard Shrugs" and correspondence, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - "Becoming Revolutionaries" (for Artforum), 2008 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - "Better Than Life" (fragment of Guggenheim intro to "Premises"), 1998 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - "The Blink Generation: Amos Poe's The Foreigner: Not Foreign Enough", undated (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - "Bloody Art", undated (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Book reviews file, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 36)
      access restricted
    - "Borderline" (on Michael Rovner), 2005 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - "Cahiers du desert", undated (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - "Cahiers du desert" - source material, undated (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - "Celine", 1983 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - "Close encounters", undated (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - "Collage", 1977 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - "Consumerism Today" - project that led to break with Sande Cohen, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - "Un continent celibataire", undated (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - "La danse des signes", undated (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - "La danse des signes" (alternate title "Delire la Gradiva"), undated (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - "La danse des signes" (on Gradiva), undated (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - "Defunkt Sex", undated (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - "Defunkt Sex", undated (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - "Délive la Gradiva" and other Freud / Nietzsche work, Undated (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - "Dépense" (incomplete), Undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - "Le Dernier mot de Saussure", Undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - "Doing Theory" for French theory conference, Undated (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - "Les Doubles" fragment, Undated (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - "Drawing on Artaud" (originally written for MOMA), Undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - "L'éffet-média", Undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - "The Empire of Evil: Modernist Literature and the Holocaust", Undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - "L'ésprit sous les mots" (unpublished), Undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - "Extreme Art", Undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - "Fétichisme and Perversion" (on Kofman), Undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - "La fiction de l'Analyse" (alternate title - "Délive la Gradiva"), Undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - "La fiction de l'analyse" (Gradiva), Undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - "La fiction de l'analyse" English translation - "The Dream Sequence", Undated (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - "La fiction de l'analyse" (Gradiva), Undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - "La fiction del'analyse", Undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - "Fictions", Undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - "Filing Dates", 1988-1999 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - "Fous d'Artaud" Latremoliére interview, c. 2002 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - "Fous d'Artaud" Ferdiére interview, c. 2002 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - "Fous d'Artaud" corrected galleys, 2002-2003 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - "Fous d'Artaud" corrected galleys - Sens and tonka, Paris, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - "Fous d'Artaud" contract with edizionimedusa, 2006 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - "The French Connection" with photos, Undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - "French Theory in America" contracts and outline, c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - "French Theory in America" draft, c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - "French Theory in America", c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - "French Theory in America": Sande / Ravelto, c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - "French Theory in America" texts for the volume, c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - "French Theory in America", c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - "French Theory in America" xeroxes and notes, c. 1998 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - "French Theory in America" review, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - "The Game of the Name" (Diacritics), c. 1973 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - "Gil Blas et le Picanesque", Undated (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - "Gradiva" - see "La fiction de l'analyse" and "La danse des signes", Undated (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - "Gradiva" - see "La fiction de l'analyse" and "La danse des signes", Undated (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - "Guggenheim Expo Catalogue" outline and notes, 1998 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Guggenheim catalogue essay, c. 1998 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Guggenheim catalogue essay materials, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Guggenheim artist clippings, Undated (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Guggenheim catalogue essay - French Art photos, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Guggenheim catalogue essay - French Architecture, 1998 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Guggenheim catalogue essay - visual materials, c. 1998 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - "Guns' Country" and other material, 1990 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - "Histoire de la [déguille]", Undated (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - "History of Semiotexte" drafts and notes 01/02/03; Published: ArtForum 80's issue, part 2, May 2003 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - "Hyperrebel" and photos, Undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - "I Talked About Antonin Artaud with Dr. L", Undated (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play presented at St. Marks Church, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play, c. 1985 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play, c. 1985 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play, c. 1985 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play fragments, c. 1985 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play - corrections, Undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" original edit (1 of 2), Undated (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" original edit (2 of 2), Undated (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play, Undated (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play - French version, Undated (Box 45, Folder 21)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" Latrémolière dialogue, Undated (Box 45, Folder 22)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play and prose texts, Undated (Box 45, Folder 23)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" play - press clipping, Undated (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" Alexander Verlag (German ed.) with correspondence, c. 1996 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud", 1997 (Box 45, Folder 26)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" resources - "A Visit to Dr. Latrémolière in [Figeac] - Notes, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - "I Talked about God with Antonin Artaud" resources - correspondence with Dr. Latrémolière, info on electroshock, c. 1985 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - "Ici New York", 1980's (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Impulse - Death Issue, Undated (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - Impulse - Death Issue - Interview with James van der Zee, Undated (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Interview by Rainer Ganahl, c. 1997 (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - "Jacques Lacan: Le pur sujet des signifiant" (unpublished), 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - "James van der Zee on my Mind", Undated (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - "Leçon de textes" (on Claud Simon) 1 of 2, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - "Leçon de textes" (on Claud Simon) 2 of 2, undated (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - for Les Lettres françaises - correspondence only (includes letters from John Irving, Philip Roth, Bernard Malamud), 1960s (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - for Les Lettres françaises - Virginia Woolf photos, circa 1962 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - for Les Lettres françaises - Virginia Woolf photos, circa 1962 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - "Les liasons dangereuses" (a play), circa 1970 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - "Lies" (Catalogue essay on Carol Irving), 1994 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - "Lisible et scriptible" (on Edith Wharton), undated (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - "Listen to Me" see also "Lost Sol", undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - "La Lit et la Lettre" (on Sade), undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - "Literature and Evil", undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - "Lost Sol" see also "Listen to Me" and "The Miracle of Lascaux", 1988 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - "Mme Bovary", 2002 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - "The man who slips" (for Rainer Ganahl catalog), circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - "The man who slips" (Berlin draft), circa 2005 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - "Michael, Funeral Director", circa 1982 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - "The Miracle of Lascaux" see also "Lost Sol", undated (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - "Les Misérables" (Bataille après tout, long version), circa 1995 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - "Les Misérables" alternate title "Les Malheureux", circa 1995 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - "Les Misérables" (on Bataille), circa 1995 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - "Les Misérables" - English version, circa 1995 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - "Motel-suicide", undated (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - "Muller-Cocktail" (includes correspondence), circa 1988 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - "Mutants", undated (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - "New York Interviews" - Intro "Confessions d'un ventriloque", circa 1983 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - "New York Interviews" - Intro "Confessions d'un ventriloque", undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - "New York Interviews" draft of "Confessions d'un ventriloque" with interview transcripts, correspondence, undated (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - "New York Interviews" draft of "Confessions d'un ventriloque" with interviews transcripts, undated (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - "New York Interviews" - copies and galleys, undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - "New York Interviews" - outline and copies, undated (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - "New York Interviews" - complete set, undated (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - "New York Interviews" - copies, undated (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - "New York Interviews" - press for German publication as "New Yorker Gespräche", 1983 (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - "No comment" (on Felix Guattari), undated (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - "An open letter to Susan Sontag", undated (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - "Oublier Artaud" Lotringer/Baudrillard "Moma" dialogue at Drawing Centre, undated (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Overexposed - correspondence, circa 1988 (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Overexposed - Dr. Stoller correspondence, confidentiality, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Overexposed - legal problems, undated (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Overexposed - Dr. Abel interviews, complete set of transcripts, undated (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Overexposed - Bob Stein transcript, undated (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Overexposed - interview transcripts "cut-ups", undated (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Overexposed - "Copy Tape #3", undated (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Overexposed - Intro, undated (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Overexposed - Intro, Undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Overexposed - Intro II, Undated (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Overexposed - Intro, Last version, Undated (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Overexposed - "Sex - chapter 2", Undated (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Overexposed - "Sex Clinic" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Overexposed - "Sex Clinic" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Overexposed - "Chapter 3 - Enjoy / Masturbatory Sessions", Undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Overexposed - Conclusion, Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Overexposed - "Conclusion: Double Talk", Undated (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Overexposed, Undated (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Overexposed, Undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Overexposed - Setting manuscript (1 of 2), Undated (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Overexposed - Setting manuscript (2 of 2), Undated (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Overexposed - Drafts and Resources, Undated (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Overexposed - Sex Clinic consent forms, French draft, Undated (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Overexposed - Resources, Undated (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Overexposed - Resources - "Sex offenses: Penal Law, Criminal Procedure Law", Undated (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Overexposed - Resources, photocopies of duty statements (BDSM, incest, pedo, rape), Undated (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Overexposed - Resources on sex offenders, Undated (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Overexposed - Resources - Sex cards, Undated (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Overexposed - Resources - Abel's "Identifying dangerous child molesters", Undated (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Overexposed - Resources - "Characteristics of Adolescent Incest Perpetrators", Undated (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Overexposed - ads, Undated (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Overexposed - cover and blurbs, Undated (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Overexposed - Publication information, Undated (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Overexposed - book launch flyers, Undated (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Overexposed - Press and promo correspondence, c. 1989 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Overexposed - Press and reactions, Undated (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Overexposed - file, press, Undated (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Overexposed - reviews, Undated (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Overexposed - contract for French publication, Undated (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Overexposed - "Surexposé" - French translation, Undated (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Overexposed - press and ongoing research on Dr. Abel, Undated (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - "Parole textamentaire", Undated (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - "Parole textamentaire" alt title "Le nouveau textament", Undated (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - "Parole textamentaire" - notes, Undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - "Peraldi", c. 2007 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - "Le philosophe et son double" and Artaud texts, Undated (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - "Playing with Fire" pm Artaud and Bataille, Undated (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - "Police Sexualities", Undated (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - "La politique des Restes" (Semio 1), c. 1974 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - "La politique des Restes:, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - "Pour une sémiotique materialiste", 1974 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Preston, John - interview and other S&M writings, Undated (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - "La Quete du Graal" - fragment, Undated (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - "Quiet day in Ivri" (on Artaud), 1990 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - "Quiet Days in Ivri", Undated (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - "Retour d'Apoétique", Undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - "Sacher-Masoch, l'humour et l'ironie" and introduction to "Venus in Furs", Undated (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - "Le Salut par les Juifs: De Bloy à Céline", Undated (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - "Savage Mind" lecture on Artaud at NYU, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - "Savoir Créer", Undated (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - "Sex in Necropolis", Undated (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - "Shell-Shocked" for Shock '88 conference, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - "Shooting Death" - Book proposal, Undated (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - "Shooting Death" - Correspondence, John Jost on Nick's Movie, Undated (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - "Shooting Death" - Connie Bessis interview, Undated (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - "Shooting Death" - Pierre Cottell interview transcript, Undated (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - "Shooting Death" - Jean Evans interview, Undated (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - "Shooting Death" - Tom Farrell interview transcript, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - "Shooting Death" - Laurie Frank interview transcript, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - "Shooting Death" - John Houseman interview transcript, Undated (Box 48, Folder 29)